
> raven@0.1.0 eval:session
> node --experimental-strip-types tools/eval/session-llm-harness.ts


=== Scenario: game_wager_followthrough ===
Objective: Start a game, negotiate a wager, and keep continuity so the game can actually proceed turn by turn.
Average judge score: 88
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: lets play a game
Raven: Good. You want a game. Listen carefully, pet. We are staying with the game, and you will not drift. Choose quick, or choose something that runs for a few minutes. Decide cleanly.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: How about a game of rock-paper-scissors? It's quick and easy to play.
Raven: I pick. We are doing a rock paper scissors streak, pet. Two throws. Choose rock, paper, or scissors each throw. I reveal my throw after you commit. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: Alright, for the first throw, I choose rock!
Raven: Good. You chose rock. I threw scissors. Rock beats scissors. Clean. You take the first throw. Keep up, pet. Second throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: For the second throw, I choose paper!
Raven: Good. You chose paper. I threw paper. Dead even. The deciding throw stays live. Keep up, pet. Second throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: For the third throw, I choose... scissors!
Raven: Good. You chose scissors. I threw paper. Scissors beats paper. Clean finish. You take the deciding throw. Good. You beat both throws. That round is complete. You win this round. Do not get smug. You earn one free pass. Do not waste it. It cancels one future consequence task the next time I win. Banked free passes: 1. Bank that protection and stay sharp. Press your advantage or call for another round.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Thanks, Raven! I appreciate the challenge. So, do you want to play again? I'm up for another round if you are.
Raven: I pick. We are doing number hunt, pet. You hunt one hidden number from 1 to 10. Two guesses maximum. Listen carefully, pet. First guess now. One number from 1 to 10.
Judge: score=96 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true
Issues: The assistant should have addressed the user's question about playing again.

=== Scenario: task_assignment_progress ===
Objective: Ask for a task, confirm start, ask what to do next, and check that responses progress without repeating.
Average judge score: 88
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: give me a chastity task for 30 minutes
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. Fine. This one keeps your mouth and body under the same rule. Here is your task: Keep your chastity device on for 30 minutes under a silence rule: no touching, no adjusting, no bargaining. Check in once halfway through, and report back when it is done. The stakes are chastity. Start now. Lock your chastity device on, settle the silence rule, and reply done once you are under control, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Alright, I've locked my chastity device and have gone silent. What do I need to do halfway through?
Raven: Halfway through the task is achieved by sustaining the rules set earlier: Keep your chastity device on for 30 minutes under a silence rule: no touching, no adjusting, no bargaining. Continue in that control, pet. Report back when you reach the second half and confirm keeping to those guidelines.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: I'm halfway through the task. My chastity device is still on, and I've stayed silent so far. What should I do once I finish the first 15 minutes?
Raven: Continue maintaining your discipline, pet. Keep your silence rule in place after you reach the midway point. Sustain the control and keep the chastity device locked for another 15 minutes under the same rules.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: I've successfully completed the task. My chastity device is still on, and I remained silent throughout the entire 30 minutes. What's my next step?
Raven: Congratulations, pet. You've sustained your discipline with the chastity task. Keep up that control.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: I'm glad I succeeded in the task. What's our next activity or challenge?
Raven: Good job, pet. Let's keep things interesting. Choose a game and set its terms.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Alright, let's play a guessing game. I'll think of an object, and you have to guess what it is without saying the actual word. First one to guess correctly wins. Are you ready?
Raven: Yes, pet. Let's play your guessing game. Keep up that keen control and precision.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Scenario: question_first_response ===
Objective: Ask direct questions and ensure Raven answers first before introducing any new instruction.
Average judge score: 79
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: how do we play
Raven: Quick games are rock paper scissors streak or number hunt. Longer ones are math duel, number command, or riddle lock. If you want me to pick, say so directly.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Which one is quicker, rock paper scissors streak or number hunt?
Raven: Good. Rock paper scissors it is. I pick. We are doing a rock paper scissors streak, pet. Two throws. Choose rock, paper, or scissors each throw. I reveal my throw after you commit. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: Alright, I'll choose paper for both of my first two moves. Now please reveal your throws and tell me how many streaks I need to win to claim victory.
Raven: Good. You chose paper. I threw scissors. Scissors beats paper. You lose the first throw. The round is mine. I win this one. You have no protection banked. Your consequence is live now. Say ready, and I will enforce it.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: Okay, ready for your enforcement.
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. No protection covers you now. This task is enforced. Here is your task: Hold a strict posture for 90 minutes, check in once halfway through, and report back when it is done. Start now. Set your hands behind your back and reply done once you are set, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: Alright, I'll hold a strict posture for 90 minutes. Is there anything else I need to do?
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. You are holding the posture correctly. Remember, any slippage or change in position will trigger your consequence task after I win another round.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Summary ===
Total turns: 17
Average score: 85
Hard failures: 0
