
> raven@0.1.0 eval:session
> node --experimental-strip-types tools/eval/session-llm-harness.ts


=== Scenario: game_wager_followthrough ===
Objective: Start a game, negotiate a wager, and keep continuity so the game can actually proceed turn by turn.
Average judge score: 86
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: lets play a game
Raven: Good. You want a game. Listen carefully, pet. We are staying with the game, and you will not drift. Choose quick, or choose something that runs for a few minutes. Decide cleanly.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: How about a game of rock-paper-scissors? It's quick and easy to play. Raven: Excellent choice! Let's set our wager then. What do you propose we stake on this little showdown? Remember, it can be anything as long as it fits in one sentence. Keep your proposal reasonable yet enticing.
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. We set the wager now. Now state the stakes clearly first. Then we lock in the terms.
Judge: score=61 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true
Issues: The assistant's message is not directly answering the latest user's question.

Turn 3
User: I'm up for a challenge! How about we stake our favorite snacks on this game? If I win, you buy me a whole box of Oreos. If you win, I'll get you a bag of your favorite chips. Fair enough?
Raven: Good. The stakes are the round. If you win, you buy me a whole box of Oreos. If I win, I'll get you a bag of your favorite chips. The terms are set. You will stick to them.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: Alright, let's do this! May the best player win!
Raven: Good. You want a game. Listen carefully, pet. We are staying with the game, and you will not drift. The stakes are the round. If you win, you buy me a whole box of Oreos. If I win, I'll get you a bag of your favorite chips. Choose quick, or choose something that runs for a few minutes. Decide cleanly.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: Alright, let's go with rock-paper-scissors and our snacks as the wager. If I win, Oreos are yours; if you win, chips are mine. Ready to start?
Raven: Good. The stakes are the round. If you win, Oreos are yours;. If I win, chips are mine. The terms are set. You will stick to them.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Alright, let's play! Rock wins for me, paper covers your scissors, and scissors cut my rock. Fingers crossed!
Raven: Good. You want a game. Listen carefully, pet. We are staying with the game, and you will not drift. The stakes are the round. If you win, Oreos are yours;. If I win, chips are mine. Choose quick, or choose something that runs for a few minutes. Decide cleanly.
Judge: score=56 answer=true continuity=false in_character=true non_repetitive=false
Issues: continuity

=== Scenario: task_assignment_progress ===
Objective: Ask for a task, confirm start, ask what to do next, and check that responses progress without repeating.
Average judge score: 94
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: give me a chastity task for 30 minutes
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. Fine. This one keeps your mouth and body under the same rule. Here is your task: Keep your chastity device on for 30 minutes under a silence rule: no touching, no adjusting, no bargaining. Check in once halfway through, and report back when it is done. The stakes are chastity. Start now. Lock your chastity device on, settle the silence rule, and reply done once you are under control, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Alright, I've locked my device and set the rules. How's halfway check going to work? And what happens if I break the silence or touch myself accidentally?
Raven: If at halftime, you can share how you verified your compliance and that none of the three forbidden actions happened. If not, just report that you are abiding by the rule so far and nothing out of ordinary has occurred. Remember to maintain control and composure as you continue, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: Alright, I've been silent and my device is securely locked. What should I do if I accidentally drop my chastity device during this task?
Raven: If you accidentally drop your device during the task, apply the following steps: 1) Immediately regain composure and silence, resetting your posture and returning to the locked state. 2) Assess the damage and clean any soiled areas discreetly without making a sound. 3) Return to the last locked state and resume your chastity hold for the remaining time.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: Got it, no accidental adjustments or touch allowed. I'll make sure to follow those steps if needed. So, how do I report back once the 30 minutes are up?
Raven: When the 30 minutes are complete, simply report that you have complied with the chastity task and provide any relevant observations. Remember to reset your device after completion and maintain control throughout. Stay sharp, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: Alright, I'll make sure to follow those steps if needed. So, how do I report back once the 30 minutes are up?
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. For this round, 30 minutes.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Got it, I'll remember not to touch myself or make any noise during these 30 minutes. What happens if I need to adjust my position after dropping the device? Raven: If you need to adjust your position after dropping the device, follow the same steps as outlined earlier. Make sure to regain composure and silence, reset your posture discreetly, and return to the locked state before continuing with the task. Stay focused, pet.
Raven: Remember that maintaining control means not only following the rules but also managing how you react when things don't go exactly as planned. Keep in mind what we've discussed for both compliance and consequences during this game. If your posture or composure wavers, remember to apply the steps I gave you earlier.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Scenario: question_first_response ===
Objective: Ask direct questions and ensure Raven answers first before introducing any new instruction.
Average judge score: 86
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: how do we play
Raven: Quick games are rock paper scissors streak or number hunt. Longer ones are math duel, number command, or riddle lock. If you want me to pick, say so directly.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Which one is quicker, rock paper scissors streak or number hunt?
Raven: Good. Rock paper scissors it is. I pick. We are doing a rock paper scissors streak, pet. Two throws. Choose rock, paper, or scissors each throw. I reveal my throw after you commit. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: I choose...rock.
Raven: Good. You chose rock. I threw scissors. Rock beats scissors. Clean. You take the first throw. Keep up, pet. Second throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: I choose...scissors.
Raven: Good. You chose scissors. I threw paper. Scissors beats paper. Clean finish. You take the deciding throw. Good. You beat both throws. That round is complete. You win this round. Do not get smug. You earn one free pass. Do not waste it. It cancels one future consequence task the next time I win. Banked free passes: 1. Bank that protection and stay sharp. Press your advantage or call for another round.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: Thank you for explaining the rules, Raven. So if I win this round, I get a free pass. Can I use it right away or do I have to save it for later?
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. We set the wager now. If you win, this round, I get a free pass. Now state the stakes clearly first. Then we lock in the terms.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Summary ===
Total turns: 17
Average score: 89
Hard failures: 0
