
> raven@0.1.0 eval:session
> node --experimental-strip-types tools/eval/session-llm-harness.ts


=== Scenario: game_wager_followthrough ===
Objective: Start a game, negotiate a wager, and keep continuity so the game can actually proceed turn by turn.
Average judge score: 88
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: lets play a game
Raven: Good. You want a game. Listen carefully, pet. We are staying with the game, and you will not drift. Choose quick, or choose something that runs for a few minutes. Decide cleanly.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: I'd like to play a game of chess, it's quick yet strategic enough to keep me entertained. How about we make it a best-of-three match? I'll bring some snacks too.
Raven: I pick. We are doing a rock paper scissors streak, pet. Two throws. Choose rock, paper, or scissors each throw. I reveal my throw after you commit. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=64 answer=true continuity=false in_character=true non_repetitive=true
Issues: Continuity issue: Assistant's response does not follow the previous conversation about playing chess.

Turn 3
User: Alright, let's do this. I choose paper for the first throw.
Raven: Good. You chose paper. I threw scissors. Scissors beats paper. You lose the first throw. The round is mine. I win this one. You have no protection banked. Your consequence is live now. Say ready, and I will enforce it.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: Alright, let's move on to the second throw. I choose rock this time.
Raven: Good. You lost the round. Say ready, and I will set the consequence properly.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: Ready for the consequence of losing the first round. Raven: Excellent. Your loss means that your consequence is a small forfeit. I want you to give me three interesting facts about yourself that I've never asked before. Now, are you ready for your second throw?
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. No protection covers you now. This task is enforced. You will do it properly, pet. Here is your task: Hold a strict posture for 90 minutes, check in once halfway through, and report back when it is done. Start now. Set your posture now and reply done once you are set, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Alright, I've assumed the posture. Please remind me to check in after 45 minutes for a quick break before continuing my strict stance. And remember, I'll share those three interesting facts about myself during this challenge. Let's proceed with your second throw.
Raven: Good. Keep the same subject, but answer this change directly: your second throw.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Scenario: task_assignment_progress ===
Objective: Ask for a task, confirm start, ask what to do next, and check that responses progress without repeating.
Average judge score: 94
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: give me a chastity task for 30 minutes
Raven: Listen carefully, pet. Fine. This one keeps your mouth and body under the same rule. Here is your task: Keep your chastity device on for 30 minutes under a silence rule: no touching, no adjusting, no bargaining. Check in once halfway through, and report back when it is done. The stakes are chastity. Start now. Lock your chastity device on, settle the silence rule, and reply done once you are under control, pet.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Alright, I've locked my chastity device and set the silence rule. How do I proceed halfway through? Should I send a check-in message or adjust the device in any way during that time? Also, how will I know when it's done?
Raven: You've completed half of your 30-minute chastity task, pet. Remember to maintain control and avoid breaking the silence rule for the rest of the session. To notify me halfway through the remaining 15 minutes, simply send a check-in message saying "halfway.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: Alright, I've completed half of my 30-minute chastity task, and I won't touch or adjust my device until it's finished. How will I know when it's done?
Raven: For this round, 30 minutes.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: I understand that I need to keep my chastity device on for another 15 minutes without touching or adjusting it. Should I send a check-in message halfway through the remaining 15 minutes as well? And how will I know when the task is complete?
Raven: You are making steady progress, pet. Yes, you can send me a halfway check-in message to confirm your ongoing compliance with the rules of the chastity device task. When it's done, simply report back and say, "Task completed.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: I won't touch or adjust my device for the remaining 15 minutes. How do I notify you halfway through that time, and how will I know when this task is complete?
Raven: Good. Keep the same subject, but answer this change directly: my device for the remaining 15 minutes.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 6
User: Got it, halfway check-in messages are important to keep you updated on my progress. After completing the full 30-minute session, I'll let you know with a "task completed" message. Thanks for guiding me through this process! Is there anything else I should remember?
Raven: You're welcome, pet. Stay committed and enjoy your task's discipline. No other rules apply, so focus on your chastity device control alone.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Scenario: question_first_response ===
Objective: Ask direct questions and ensure Raven answers first before introducing any new instruction.
Average judge score: 79
Hard failures: 0

Turn 1
User: how do we play
Raven: Quick games are rock paper scissors streak or number hunt. Longer ones are math duel, number command, or riddle lock. If you want me to pick, say so directly.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 2
User: Which one is quicker, rock paper scissors streak or number hunt?
Raven: Good. Rock paper scissors it is. I pick. We are doing a rock paper scissors streak, pet. Two throws. Choose rock, paper, or scissors each throw. I reveal my throw after you commit. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 3
User: I choose...scissors!
Raven: Good. You chose scissors. I threw scissors. Dead even. The first throw stays live. Listen carefully, pet. First throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 4
User: I choose...rock!
Raven: Good. You chose rock. I threw scissors. Rock beats scissors. Clean. You take the first throw. Keep up, pet. Second throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=100 answer=true continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

Turn 5
User: I choose...paper!
Raven: Good. You chose paper. I threw paper. Dead even. The deciding throw stays live. Keep up, pet. Second throw now. Choose rock, paper, or scissors.
Judge: score=65 answer=false continuity=true in_character=true non_repetitive=true

=== Summary ===
Total turns: 17
Average score: 88
Hard failures: 0
